<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="ANZ_supported_app_versions">
        <item>5.0.7</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="helpQuestions_General">
        <item>What is this?</item>
        <item>What happens if my device malfunctions or gets bricked?</item>
        <item>But can\'t I just use RootCloak?</item>
        <item>How do we know your not storing our sensitive account information?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="helpAnswers_General">
        <item>
            This is a Xposed application which hooks on the ANZ GoMoney and/or Semble to bypass
            certain root checks the application does so we can use rooted and non-supported devices
            with GoMoney Wallet or Semble Services respectively.
        </item>
        <item>
            As a rooted user I suspect you knew the risks. I placed a disclaimer within this
            application that states I, ANZ or Semble and their partners will not be responsible
            for any worst case scenarios. To avoid bricking, do a full (nandroid) backup just in
            case anything happens. The likelihood of something happening is very slim, but don\'t
            take unnecessary chances.

            USE AT YOUR OWN RISK, YOU HAVE BEEN WARNED.
        </item>
        <item>
            RootCloak rarely works for banking applications as the source code used is too generic
            to target all applications hence why it doesn\'t work for Semble or ANZ GoMoney hence
            why this application was created.
        </item>
        <item>
            I have no intention of doing that. If you are truly paranoid, the source code is on
            GitHub which can be viewed on the main menu of this module. There you can see for
            yourself that there is no code storing bank information.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="helpQuestions_ANZ">
        <item>Why does the "Spoof Device" feature do?</item>
        <item>What happens if ANZ GoMoney NZ Mods says that it is not compatible?</item>
        <item>Does this work for ANZ GoMoney Australia?</item>
        <item/>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="helpAnswers_ANZ">
        <item>
            This changes the way your device appears to ANZ GoMoney application. You only need
            this enabled if your mobile phone is not on the ANZ GoMoney Compatibility List but
            know it has NFC with HCE support. Also this does not guarantee that NFC payment will
            work as this is a Beta feature but also because yhere are some devices out there that
            simply will never work due to software or hardware restrictions. Furthermore, this app
            does NOT modify \'build.prop\' so it will only affect the ANZ GoMoney application, not
            the entire system which would be impractical.
            \n\n
            If spoofing is enabled, you MUST clear all cache and data of the ANZ GoMoney
            application and re-login. So keep your Account Number and password on hand.
        </item>
        <item>
            Then Root detection (and device spoofing if enabled) is disabled. This may mean that
            GoMoney Wallet (NFC Payment) will be deactivated. You\'ll have to wait till Xposed
            Installer tells you that the xposed module needs updating. You\'ll need to
            follow the instructions below..
            \n\n
            1. Update the xposed module via Xposed Installer (Should be already enabled, but check just incase)\n
            2. Restart Device\n
            3. Open the ANZ New Zealand GoMoney Mods UI Application\n
            4. Enable the features you like\n
            5. Restart Device\n
            6. Open GoMoney app, check if your changes are in effect (like if GoMoney Wallet appears in the settings). If they are then your\'re done, If not, then jump to step 7.\n
            7. Clear all data and cache of the ANZ GoMoney app\n
            8. Restart Device\n
            9. Login to the application for the first time (Account Number and password required)\n
            10. Done!
        </item>
        <item>
            No. I think the ANZ GoMoney Australia application is different from the New Zealand
            version therefore don\'t expect compatibility even after Australia gets NFC Mobile
            Payment features. AND STOP CLAIMING THE PAVLOVA IS YOURS!!!
        </item>
        <item/>
    </string-array>
</resources>
