<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="helpQuestions_General">
        <item>Note about Help and FAQ\'s</item>
        <item>What is this?</item>
        <item>But can\'t I just use RootCloak?</item>
        <item>How do we know your not storing our sensitive account information?</item>
        <item>Why are some of the application settings disabled?</item>
        <item>What does the "Spoof Device" feature do when enabled for Semble and ANZ GoMoney?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="helpAnswers_General">
        <item>
            Although the information here is still relevant, it is also very limited simply because
            it cannot list all FAQ\'s, known issues and bugs. For more helpful and in-depth support,
            its recommended to read the XDA thread.
        </item>
        <item>
            This is a Xposed module application which hooks on the ANZ GoMoney, Semble
            and TVNZ OnDemand and 3NOW to bypass certain root detection so users that have rooted and/or
            non-supported devices can use GoMoney Wallet, Semble services and watch OnDemand videos
            respectively.
        </item>
        <item>
            RootCloak rarely works for banking applications as the source code used is too generic
            to target all applications. In this specific case, RootCloak doesn\'t work properly
            with Semble or ANZ GoMoney NZ hence why this application was created.
        </item>
        <item>
            I have no intention of doing that. If you are truly paranoid, the source code is
            available on GitHub which can be reached by going to 3-dot settings on the main activity
            of this module. There you can see for yourself that there is no code storing bank
            information or sending it off to a remote server or anything like that. This application
            doesn\'t even have the android permissions "android.permission.INTERNET" anyways.
        </item>
        <item>
            If an option is disabled it means the application used for those tweaks is not
            installed. For instance, if I dont have any of the variants of Semble (either from
            Vodafone, 2Degrees of Spark), the option is disabled because it would provide no
            additional benefits of having it enabled.
        </item>
        <item>
            This changes the way your device appears to ANZ GoMoney or the Semble application. You only need
            this enabled if your mobile phone is not on the ANZ GoMoney Wallet or Semble compatibility list but
            know your device has NFC with HCE support. This feature does not guarantee that NFC payment will
            work because there are some devices out there that simply will never work due
            to software or hardware restrictions.
            \n\n
            The difference between this and other spoofing applications is this module does NOT modify
            \'build.prop\' so it will only affect the ANZ GoMoney and Semble application, not
            the entire system which would be impractical.
            \n\n
            If spoofing is enabled for ANZ GoMoney, you MUST clear all cache and data of the ANZ GoMoney
            application and re-login. So keep your Account Number and password handy. This is not
            necessary for Semble though.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="helpQuestions_ANZ">
        <item>When toggling features for ANZ GoMoney, why do you always state I need to clear the cache and data of the ANZ GoMoney?</item>
</string-array>

    <string-array name="helpAnswers_ANZ">
        <item>
            There is two reasons I tell you to do this. Firstly, the ANZ GoMoney Application has
            checks for root on boot as well as when you launch the application. When it detects
            root access, it disables all GoMoney Wallet features even if it was previously enabled.
            To re-activate these settings, the only way to do this is to reset application
            completely by clearing the cache and data. Another reason, which mainly
            applies mainly to the "Spoof Device" feature is that the application needs to be reset as
            device registration only happens on first-time run of the application hence why
            clearing cache and data is needed.
            \n\n
            When toggling the option to enable screenshots, you do not need to clear the data or cache.
            Next time you open the application, the setting you choose will be in place.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
